http://www.holts.com/privacy-policy

My AccountCustomer ServiceHolt's Clubhouse
Search site:
Sign Up
Subscribing, please wait...
0
Close
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Home
Cigars
All Cigar Brands
New Arrivals
6-Packs To Go!
Ashton CigarsArturo Fuente CigarsOliva
CigarsLa Aroma de Cuba CigarsPadron CigarsRomeo y Julieta CigarsSan Cristobal CigarsMy Father CigarsPerdomo CigarsNub CigarsMontecristo CigarsDavidoff CigarsPunch CigarsRocky Patel CigarsAlec Bradley Cigars
Price Per Cigar
Under $2$2 - $4$4 - $6$6 - $8$8 and Up
Prices
Cheap CigarsDollar Store CigarsEvery Day Value CigarsExpensive Cigars
Rating
Top Rated CigarsMost Reviewed Cigars
Shape
Corona CigarsChurchill CigarsRobusto CigarsCigarillo CigarsPerfecto CigarsTorpedo CigarsToro CigarsLancero CigarsBelicoso CigarsPanetela CigarsGiant CigarsLonsdale CigarsGordo CigarsDouble Corona CigarsPetit Corona Cigars
Wrapper
Cameroon CigarsCandela CigarsConnecticut CigarsCorojo CigarsHabano CigarsMaduro CigarsNatural CigarsSan Andres CigarsSumatra Cigars
Size
Big CigarsFat CigarsSmall CigarsShort CigarsLong Cigars
Country of Origin
Dominican CigarsHonduran CigarsMexican CigarsNicaraguan CigarsAmerican Cigars
Strength
Mild CigarsMedium CigarsStrong CigarsFull Strength Cigars
Samplers
All Samplers
Featured Samplers
Brand Samplers
Monster Deals
Cigar of the Month Club
Build Your Own Sampler
Top Samplers
Oliva Master Blends Monster DealLa Aroma de Cuba & La Gloria Cubana Monster Deal'Royal Flush' Super SamplerRocky Patel 'Luxury Collection' SamplerAshton 5-Cigar AssortmentLa Aroma de Cuba 5-Cigar Assortment Alec Bradley 'All-Star' SamplerRomeo y Julieta & Montecristo Monster DealNub 'Stub Club' Monster Deal'Connecticut Cream' Monster Deal
Price Per Cigar
Under $2$2 - $4$4 - $6$6 - $8$8 and Up
Prices
$30 and Under$30 - $50$50 - $70$70 and Up
Rating
Top Rated SamplersMost Reviewed Samplers
Packaging
Cigar Sampler BoxCigar Sampler Pack
Strength
Mild Strength Cigar SamplersMedium Strength Cigar SamplersFull Strength Cigar Samplers
Specials
Weekly Special
Top Shelf Showcase
1 Day Flash Sale
Freebie Deals
Premium Price Buster
Top Deals
6-Packs To Go!Holt's Factory SpecialsOliva Master Blends Monster DealNat Sherman PanamericanaRocky Patel 'Luxury Collection' SamplerMacanudo Heritage NuevoCusano MaduroVilliger Cuellar KremeAlec Bradley Family BlendRoom 101 Master Collection Three
Hottest Deals
Cigar of the Month Club
Monster Deals
Clearance
Gift Cards
Sweepstakes
Cigar Mugs
Free Shipping
Top Accessories
Xikar HP4 Quad Torch LighterSavoy Steel CutterAshton Black AshtrayXikar Xi1 CutterSavoy Mahogany Glass Top HumidorVisol Artemis Triple Torch LighterBovedaArtisan Champagne HumidorAshton Tan Calfskin Leather CaseVisol Sawtooth Cutter
Humidors
Travel HumidorsSavoy HumidorsDesktop Humidors
Ashtrays
Outdoor AshtraysGlass AshtraysVintage AshtraysCar Ashtrays1-2 Finger Ashtrays2-4 Finger Ashtrays5+ Finger Ashtrays
Lighters
Torch LightersButane LightersCigar LightersWindproof LightersXikar LightersColibri LightersJetline LightersVisol Lighters
Cigar Cases
Leather Cigar Cases2-Finger Cigar Cases3-Finger Cigar Cases
Cutters
Guillotine CuttersXikar CuttersPunch CuttersV-Cutters
Humidification
Cigar Humidifier BeadsCigar Humidifier CrystalsElectronic Cigar Humidifiers Cigar Humidifier PouchesCigar Humidifier Sticks
Cigar Apparel
Cigar Shirts for MenCigar Shirts for WomenCigar Hats
By Brand
Xikar AccessoriesSavoy AccessoriesColibri AccessoriesVisol AccessoriesHumi-Care Accessories
Gift Guide
Gift Cards
Gifts under $50
Gifts Under $100
Gifts over $100
It’s a Boy / It’s a Girl Cigars
Christmas & Holiday Cigar Gifts
Top Gift Items
Ashton 10-Cigar SamplerRocky Patel 'Red Carpet' Collection'Royal Flush' Super SamplerST Dupont Maxi Jet Torch LighterLa Aroma de Cuba '93-95 Rated' Super SamplerAshton Ice Carved Crystal AshtrayPadron Family Reserve Maduro SamplerArturo Fuente 'Journey Through Time' AshtraySavoy Executive Ebony Macassar HumidorXikar Burnout Ashtray
Gifts by Occasion
New BabyBirthdayWeddingGroomsmen Golfing
Cigar of the Month Club
Monthly Membership
3-Month Membership
6-Month Membership
12-Month Membership
Gifts by Price
Gifts Under $25Gifts $25 - $50Gifts $50 - $75Gifts $75 - $100Gifts $100 - $200Gifts Over $200
Gifts by Experience
Cigars for BeginnersGifts for Cigar Lovers
Home
>
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Holt’s Cigar Company is firmly committed to the protection and respect of your privacy.  Following, we will outline our policy regarding the collection and use of information obtained from our customers, visitors and guests.  If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, or if you would like to unsubscribe from receiving any communications from Holt’s, you may Contact Us at any time.
Maintaining your privacy is a crucial priority at Holt’s.  We do not sell, share or rent your information to other parties in any manner other than expressly disclosed in this statement.
Please review our Privacy Policy for a clear understanding of the measures we employ to protect you and guard the information you provide to us.  By visiting www.holts.com, you are accepting the practices outlined in this document. All California residents have additional rights provided by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018("CCPA"). You may review your rights under the "CCPA" here.
Information Collected
We collect and store the information you enter on our website, as well as any information you provide to us in any other way.  You may choose not to provide certain information, but as a result you may be prohibited from accessing specific attributes of online shopping.
Why We Request Your Information
Holt’s collects information about customers for the purpose of enhancing site navigation, expediting order placement and providing an overall exceptional online shopping experience.  Complete satisfaction and superior customer service from your initial order placement to the product reaching your doorstep are fundamental priorities at Holt’s.  The creation and collection of login and password information, for example, save you time throughout the order process.
How We Request Your Information
We prompt you to supply your contact, billing and shipping information as you create an account during the order process.  This information is required to complete a purchase and is used to contact you regarding your order.
Correct billing, shipping and contact information, such as email and phone number, are necessary for Holt’s to process your order.  Transfer of this information is secure and cannot be received or accessed by others.  We share your credit card information only with our bank for the purpose of authorization.
How We Use Information We Request
Third parties are utilized to perform services in conjunction with Holt’s operations.  Payment processing and authorization, fraud protection, age verification, order fulfillment and shipping, website evaluation, data analysis, as well as the distribution of marketing materials are all examples of third party services used by Holt’s.  Personal information provided to third parties by Holt’s is authorized for use only in conjunction with the services third parties perform.
California Privacy Act Disclosure
The California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) provides consumers who are California residents with explicit rights regarding their personal information.
Holt’s Cigar Company does not sell your personal information.
You have the right to request deletion of the personal information collected or maintained by Holt’s Cigar Company. Deletion of personal information may affect our ability to manage your account.
You have the right to request that Holt’s Cigar Company disclose what personal information we collect, use, and disclose, including:
Categories of personal information we collected about you.
Categories of sources from which we collected the personal information.
Business or commercial purposes for collecting your personal information.
Categories of third parties with whom we share the personal information.
Specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
In order to protect your information from unauthorized deletion or disclosure, we will verify your request using three pieces of Personal Information that can be verified against data previously collected from you and in our systems.
Only you, or someone legally authorized to act on your behalf (your designated authorized agent), may make a verifiable consumer request related to your Personal Information.
We will request your name, mailing address, and email address from you in order to complete the verification process. We will also request some additional information, such as: last four digits of your credit card, last item ordered, date of last order, total dollar charge of last order, last item you returned or name of person you have shipped to in the past.
When it is not possible to match three pieces of Personal Information, we may engage a third-party verification service to avoid fraudulent or malicious intent.
We will only use personal information provided for this purpose of verifying your identity or authority to make the request.
When we are not able to verify your request, we must deny the request, but will communicate the reason for such denial to you.
We will not discriminate against you because you exercised your rights under this section of the Privacy Policy.
For purposes of exercising your rights above, please note how we collected and used your personal information:
We collect the following categories of personal information:
Identifiers (name, date of birth, postal address, telephone numbers, online identifiers, Internet Protocol address, email address, driver’s license or other similar identifiers); personal information listed in the CA Customer Records statute (such as payment information); commercial information; internet or other electronic network activity information; geolocation data; audio, electronic, or visual information; sensory data, such as audio and visual recordings; inferences drawn from other personal information, such as: your preferences and behaviors.
We disclose the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:
Identifiers; personal information listed in the CA Customer Records statute (such as payment information); characteristics of protected classifications under the California or federal law; commercial information; internet of other electronic network activity information; geolocation data; inferences drawn from other personal information, such as: your preferences and behaviors.
We disclose personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of Service Providers:
Shipping companies, age verification providers, military and first responder verification providers, printing companies, technology companies, cloud service providers, analytics companies, fraud protection and investigation companies, payment processors, credit card issuers, media companies/platforms.
Right to Know
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information, including the categories and specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you. You may submit a Right to Know request on our contact us page or call us at 1-800-523-1641. If emailing, please reference Right to Know in the subject line. We will confirm receipt of your request within 10 days.
We will respond to a verifiable consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to an additional 45 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. We will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. You may make a Right to Know request up to twice in a 12-month period.
If you have an account with us, we will deliver our written response to that account. If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our written response by mail.
Right to Delete
You have the right to request deletion of your Personal Information that we collected or maintain, subject to certain exceptions in the CCPA. You may submit a Right to Delete request on our contact us page. If emailing, please reference Right to Delete in the subject line.
Impacts of deletion include:
Your purchase history will no longer be accessible
We will not be able to look up your transactions for returns, previous gifts, or repairs
You will be required to provide a receipt for any future returns
If you have an account on Holt’s Cigar Company, it will be deleted
Please note, we will continue to maintain limited information needed to comply with fraud prevention, and other legal and business requirements.
In order to delete your information, the following steps are required by the law:
You submit a request to delete, and
We will separately confirm with you that you want your information deleted.
If we are unable to verify a Request for Delete, your request will be treated as a request to Opt-Out and we will notify you. Once we receive and confirm your deletion request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, within 45 days, unless an exception applies.
Alternatives to Deleting Your Personal Information
We do have alternatives if you are unsure if deleting your personal information is the best option for you. Please feel free to visit our contact us page, or email us at holts@holts.com or call 1-800-523-1641 to inquire about the following:
Removal from our catalog mailing list
Unsubscribing from emails
If you simply want to stop receiving emails or physical catalogs, please feel free to visit our contact us page or call us 1-800-523-1641. If emailing, please reference Catalog Opt Out or Unsubscribe from Emails in the subject line.
Do Not Sell My Personal Information
Holt’s Cigar Company does not sell your personal information.
Emails
Receive exclusive weekly email specials from Holt’s by signing up with your email address.  You will be eligible for all of our weekly deals and discounts.  If you prefer to discontinue receipt of these specials, please Contact Us.  We also use your email address to provide you with order confirmation emails and invoices.
Request a Catalog
Holt’s publishes a monthly catalog which may be sent to you for showing an interest in our products.  If you wish to be removed from our catalog mailing list, Contact Us at any time.
Edit Your Personal Information
To edit your personal information at anytime, Contact Us.  A customer’s web information cannot be altered over the phone.  Additionally, you may change your personal information online anytime you log into your account.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
You will be notified via email in the event that our Privacy Policy is modified in a manner that will affect your personally identifiable information.
Opt Out
At any time, you may opt out of receiving any communications from Holt’s.  Contact Us directly and we will expedite your request for removal.
Cookies
Cookies store information about a customer’s shopping cart and are used to identify how a person arrived at Holt’s.  While you are visiting www.holts.com, a cookie identifies you and keeps track of the items in your shopping cart between visits.  Cookies are stored locally to your computer and are only read by www.holts.com.  Cookies do not contain credit card information.
Security
The protection of your privacy and personal information is a major priority at Holt’s.  We utilize industry-standard systems and procedures to safeguard against unauthorized access to information collected online and to ensure that it is used appropriately.
Holt’s uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide during transmission.  All of your information, including credit card numbers, is encrypted so that it cannot be read during its exchange over the internet.  In addition, we recommend protecting unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.  Sign off and close all browsers whenever using a shared computer.
Contests & Sweepstakes
Entrant grants to Holt’s a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free license to edit, publish, promote, republish at any time in the future and otherwise use Entrant’s submitted photo, along with Entrant’s name, likeness, biographical information, and any other information provided by Entrant, in any and all media for possible editorial, promotional or advertising purposes, without further permission, notice or compensation (except where prohibited by law).
Customer Testimonials
Contact
Us
Request A Catalog
Support
The Troops
Retail
Stores
Subscribing, please wait...
Holt’s Cigar Company does not sell cigars, or tobacco-related products to anyone under the age of 21.
Our website does not sell cigarettes, e-cigs, or vape. If you are not of legal age, please do not enter our site.
Copyright © 2020 Holt's Cigar Company. All Rights Reserved.
